uh another tutorial and i'll be sharing
with you so today we're gonna be talking
about beneficiary change requests and
the purpose of this is to make sure that
you can put your designated beneficiary
so
i do have tons of clients which is uh
close to 500 now and some of them okay
their beneficiaries died last year or a
couple of months ago somebody just got
married so for example okay uh you are a
sunlight financial uh client so you go
ahead and simply
communicate with me as your financial
advisor i'll be
asking you to fill out this form so
conor 08
and then all these uh account numbers
that give me 9
and then last name mo let's say for
example um
you are
de la cruz right
and your
first name is
vladimir okay
and then celensky
all right so now
um since you're in the individual
account so you need to understand
okay so are you asking us to add the
beneficiary
remove a beneficiary
or
change your beneficiary information now
the next question that you might be
asking is is it possible
yes possible all right so
if you're going to be adding a
beneficiary so page uh well proceed to
item 2 and 17 then complete uh the items
21 on words now
uh your beneficiary is actually your
husband already so wipe let's say for
example because it's vladimir now hey uh
de la cruz
last name is change
zero one and then month will be october
okay
and then
nine
nine eighteen
1989 okay okay let's go directly with
this one now unrevocable uh beneficiary
and designation about is
uh
you don't need to ask permission
whenever you're making some changes or
if you're going to be putting
irrevocable so every time i'm going to
change the vladimir
okay she needs to contact
uh his wife wanna be changed all right
to understand this portion right okay
country of birth
russia
okay so for example citizenship
ukrainian
okay
okay so she's holding now uh
spouse okay
okay and at the same time
primary okay so i highly recommend that
you go ahead and simply put the details
directly at either the primary or
contingent pero hindi wedding boat okay
so primary
in um
it can be sold primary or it can be
included directly with the primary
beneficiaries like sustain capacity
contingent
in the event of all the primary
beneficiaries will uh will die let's say
for example
let's say for example philippines so
complete address
for example i'm just giving you an
example
makati
philippines in uh so
make sure to include that one so bowel
um
next
okay
beneficiary um
well i don't recommend you to put your
underage kids uh
primary beneficiary i highly recommend
you go ahead and put them directly sir
miss moon okay
um
mismo contingent for example now in the
ilaguni vladimir or
ablation and life insurance okay
okay
18 years old uh 16 years old
nc
okay
de la cruz 13 years old
directly from
the miss mong
first marriage
has a first relationship yeah
that's the main reason why we need to
remove them is because they are still
underage
okay if you want them to be put directly
foreign
and then provide all the details and
then put them directly second in general
all right
next
okay change of beneficiary information
all right
now uh let me piggyback a little bit
okay do something remove beneficiaries
all right
and uh
information okay
in details detail for individual
policyholder and then
submit it
directly
okay um signature of the policy owner
okay signature
and then print the name
okay so for example
um
signature okay
okay tapos
name and all
all right now
signature of witness after muslim assign
danto
kindly take note that i'll be
the
the witness itself okay then please
subscribe
okay so that's what i'd like you to uh
to emphasize and then sign up john okay
and then lastly
um
changes in terms of your contact
information
all right and that's it guys all right
so that's how you
will go ahead and make things happen so
do you have any questions or feel free
to
get in touch with me or
leave a comment on the section below
alright
[Music]
you